But my point is that we buy insurance to protect ourselves financially in case those things happen, right? So by investing sustainably we're doing two things. We're creating insurance, reducing the risk to our planet and to our economy, and at the same time, in the short term, we're not sacrificing performance. [Man in comic: "What if it's a big hoax and we create a better world for nothing?"] Good, you like it. I like it too. (Laughter) I like it because it pokes fun at both sides of the climate change issue. I bet you can't guess which side I'm on. But what I really like about it is that it reminds me of something Mark Twain said, which is, "Plan for the future, because that's where you're going to spend the rest of your life." Thank you. (Applause)
Pero mi idea es que contratamos seguros para cubrirnos económicamente si esto sucediera, ¿sí? Por eso al hacer inversiones sustentables estamos haciendo 2 cosas. Estamos creando un seguro, reduciendo el riesgo para nuestro planeta y para nuestra economía, y al mismo tiempo, a corto plazo, no estamos sacrificando el rendimiento. [Hombre en la tira: "¿Y si es broma y hacemos un mundo mejor para nada?"] Bueno, les gustó. A mí también. (Risas) Me gusta porque se ríe de los dos lados del cambio climático. ¿A que adivinan de qué lado estoy? Pero lo que más me gusta es que me hace acordar a algo que dijo Mark Twain: "Planea para el futuro, porque ahí es donde vas a pasar el resto de tu vida". Gracias. (Aplausos)